本字幕由 PTT同志影视作品板 2013重新校稿
原字幕取自网路资源  仅供学习 禁用任何商业盈利行为
校稿：Coldsis、hahanjia、mohiwa
同志亦凡人 Queer As Folk S01E15
他十一点左右要小睡一下
So he takes a nap around 11:00,
到了三点还要睡一会儿
And another one around 3:00.
真不赖
Lucky him.
咕噜  咕噜  咕噜
Glug, glug, glug.
还有紧急联络的号码
And all the emergency numbers...
噢  如果你要带他出去
Oh, and if you want to take him outside,
别忘了帮他戴上小童帽
Don't forget to put his little beanie hat on.
他真是可爱
He looks so adorable.
有人看到过我的另一只鞋了吗
Has anyone, uh, seen my other shoe?
是这个在我屁股下的东西吗?
Ah, is that what I'm sitting on?
我就知道这不是我常用的橡胶玩具 (假阳具)
I knew it wasn't one of my usual rubber toys.
布莱恩  你有在认真听吗
Brian, are you listening to me?
有  吃饭时间
Yeah, feeding time,
睡觉时间  小童帽
Nap time, beanie hat.
我记住了
I got it.
我会好好照顾他的  琳赛
He's going to be fine, Lindsay.
我相信你
I know he will be.
仓促通知下你也肯帮忙  我很感激
And I appreciate you doing this on such short notice.
但我现在得回去工作了
But now that I have to go back to work,
不得不去参加这个该死的教师会议
I have to attend this damn teachers' conference.
也许你能邂逅一个漂亮的美女体育老师
Well, maybe you'll meet a nice lady P.E. Teacher.
不用担心
Don't worry.
我也会帮忙看着他的
I'll keep an eye on him too.
我才不需要你来帮忙看着他
I don't need you to keep an eye on him.
我是说看着你
I meant you.
我是他爸  我能照顾好他
I'm his father, I'm not going to fuck it up.
你能说服他们信任我吗
Would you please tell them to give me some credit?
我信任你
I am.
所以我才把他交给你
That's why I'm leaving him in your care.
屁话
Bullshit.
你之所以把他交给我
You're leaving him with me
是因为茉蕾妮去迈阿密看她的长舌妇老妈
Because Melanie's going to go see her yenta mother In Miami
礼拜天之前都回不来
and won't be back till Sunday.
这是我开会地方的电话号码
Here's my number at the conference.
给你
There you go.
他不会有事的  孩子的娘
He's going to be fine, mom.
我知道  孩子的爸
I know, dad.
我爱你
Love you.
准备好跟你老爸一起
Are you ready to spend a weekend
度过一个愉快的周末了吗  阳光小宝贝
with your old man, sonny-boy?
-我走了     - 等等  迈克
- I'm off.  - Whoa, whoa, Michael!
你能帮我搬一下这些东西吗
You want to give me a hand with some of this stuff, please?
拜托  客房都被塞满了
Come on, I know there's a guest room up here somewhere.
抱歉  我本要把我的东西清一清的
I'm sorry, I was going to move some of my stuff.
- 所以，他几点钟到             -七点半
- So, when's he arriving?  - 7:30.
如果飞机准时的话
If the plane's on time.
你一定很兴奋吧
You must be pretty excited.
我整个夏天都盼着今天呢
I've been counting the days all summer.
望眼欲穿啊
That's a long time.
是啊  俄勒冈离这儿很远
Yeah, well, Oregon's a long way away.
幸亏有电子邮件
Thank god for e-mail.
我还在他的好友列表里呢
I'm on his buddy list.
-你一定会爱上我儿子                              -酷
-God, you're going to love my son.  -Cool.
你真该见见这孩子  他太棒了
You should see this kid. He-he's amazing.
他聪明  他风趣
He's smart, he's funny.
他  他会吹高音萨克斯  他会做网站
He... h-he plays tenor sax, he can do web sites,
他还会杂耍
He can... he juggles.
真强  那他还有时间做脑科手术吗？
Great. When does he find time for brain surgery?
啊  他听起来很了不起
Ah... he sounds marvellous.
他是了不起
He is.
他会喜欢你的
He's going to love you too.
你又知道了
How do you know that?
谁不呢?
Who wouldn't?
我没看过你穿这件
I have not seen these before.
未来，如果你够幸运的话
Well one day, if you're lucky,
你可能会看到
You just might.
-工作愉快                                 -你也是
-Have a good day at work.  -You too.
你就不能穿的更低调一些吗
Couldn't you have worn something a little more discreet?
只要盖住你黑色三角地带
As long as your erogenous zones are covered,
你就算得上穿着保守了
you're safely in the conservative column.
而且我也试过异性恋那套什麽「见到曙光」的狗屁
Besides, I tried straight drag, "saw the light".
谢天谢地
Thank you, god.
现在
Now...
午餐吃什麽？
What're you in the mood for, for lunch?
嗯  寿司怎麽样
How about, uh, sushi?
啊  食物中毒 正是我需要的
Ah, just what I need, food poisoning.
好吧  印度菜呢
Okay, Indian?
胃食道逆流
Heartburn.
-猪排呢    -心脏病
- Ribs?     -Heart attack.
你知道我想吃什麽吗
Y-you know what I could really go for?
面包夹金枪鱼  涂上双份的蛋黄酱
Tuna fish on white bread, double mayo,
洋芋片 凉拌卷心菜  香草布丁
Potato chips, coleslaw, vanilla pudding.
你不是每天都吃这些吗
That's what you have every day. Well...
泰德
Ted?
泰德·施密特
Ted Schmidt?
-戴尔·威克斯勒  -对
- Dale Wexler?  - Yeah.
是阿  我们多久没见了
Yeah, how long's it been?
呃  好多年了
Ah... years.
噢  这是我朋友  艾美特
Oh, uh, this is my friend, Emmett.
他不是干咱们这行的
He's not from these parts.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我也是
You too.
上次听到你的消息
So, uh, last thing I heard
说你要在巴尔的摩开公司
You were setting up offices in Baltimore?
还有辛辛那提  现在发展到这儿了
And Cincinnati. Now here.
太棒了  你的事业蒸蒸日上啊
It's great, you're doing so well.
当然了  我们早知道你前途无量
I mean, we all knew you would, of course.
是啊  我过的还不错  你呢?
Yeah, life's been good. How about you?
我还在原来那个公司上班呢
Yeah, I'm still working for the same firm.
天啊  我以为你早就离开温斯福特了呢
Christ, I thought you would have left Wertschafter by now.
是啊  他的个人魅力和慷慨大度
Yeah, well, his personal appeal and selfless generosity,
实在让我不忍离开
they're just hard to resist.
刚好，我得和一个客户去吃饭
Listen, I, uh, got to meet a client for lunch,
那个新开的印尼餐馆  你去过吗
This new Indonesian place. You tried it?
他
Him?
呃  还没有  不过我有打算要去
Um, no. Not yet, but I-I'm meaning to.
见到你很开心
Nice to see you.
我也是
Yeah, same here.
那是谁啊
Who was that?
是我在商学院的同学
Ah, someone I went to business school with.
嗯…他真帅
Hmm, he's cute.
我以前也那麽觉得
I thought so too.
听说他是个行动派
I hear he's a real mover.
30岁之前就成了百万富翁
Became a millionaire before he was 30.
真想知道他的成功秘诀
Wonder what his secret is.
我永远也无法知道
I'll probably never know.
这个12岁的魔术师
And apparently this 12-year-old juggling,
还会玩爵士乐的网路天才
Jazz-playing web-master...
他要是讨厌我怎麽办？
What if he hates me?
谁啊
Who?
-大卫的儿子     - 去他的  只不过是个孩子
- David's son.  - Fuck him, he's just a kid.
他不只是个孩子  他是大卫的孩子
He's not just a kid, he's David's son.
你知道这意味着什麽
And you know what that means.
你就是那个恶毒的後母
You're the wicked stepmother.
什麽
What?
你就是那个恶毒的後母
You're the wicked stepmother.
像童话故事里的一样
Like in fairy tales.
你怎麽不带着你故事书回去工作？
Well, why don't you get your fairy tail back to work.
不是还有很多马桶等着你刷亮吗
Isn't there a toilet you need to spit-shine?
别这麽可怜兮兮  小迈  他才不会讨厌你
Don't be so pathetic, Mikey. He's not going to hate you.
你怎麽知道
Well, what makes you so sure?
连我都爱死你了
I'm crazy about you.
你这是怎麽了
What is with you?
他说得对
He's right.
我就是…那个後母
I'm... I'm the stepmother.
我  是那个後母
I'm... me, a stepmother.
谁是後母
Who's a stepmother?
小迈
Mikey.
大卫的儿子周末要来
David's son's coming in for the weekend.
啥?
Huh?
你怎麽会这麽想呢？
What do you think of that?
看看你呀  你真漂亮
Look at you, you're so beautiful.
我发誓  布莱恩
I swear to god, Bbrian,
他会一天天地更像你
He's getting to look more like you every day, yes.
是的  不过头发还得再下下功夫
Yeah, well, we're still working on the hair.
琳赛去哪儿了
Where's Lindsay?
她去开一个教师会议
She's at a teachers' conference,
所以这周末我来照顾他
So I'm watching him for the weekend.
你?
You?
我连植物都不放心给你照顾
I'd be afraid to let you water my plants.
你知道帮宝适是什麽吗
Do you even know what a Huggie is?
那可不是什麽性爱体位
It's not a sexual position.
我当然知道  那是  呃
Of course I do. It's, um, uh...
一种尿布
A diaper!
噢  是的
Oh... yeah,
我最了解尿布了
I know all about diapers.
我和一个大公司的总裁
I was fucking this guy for a while,
胡搞过一阵子
CEO of a big corporation.
他喜欢上穿着尿布  要我打他的屁股
He used to like to wear diapers when I spanked him.
恶心
Gross.
变态
It's kinky.
这周末不是皮衣舞会吗
Isn't this weekend the leather ball?
我还以为你会忙着参加呢
I would think that your dance card would be full.
我知道  那很有诱惑力  但是
I know, it's tempting, but...
今年
This year,
我得把我的皮内裤
I'm trading in my leather jockstrap...
换成
For...
尿不湿
Rubber pants.
对不对呢  小宝贝儿
Isn't that right, sonny-boy?
请弗兰克·劳德乘客到美国航空的
Paging passenger Frank Lord to the American Airlines...
迈克  汉克来了
Michael, there's Hank.
好吧  终於来了
Okay, here we go.
旅行愉快  再见
Have a nice visit. Bye.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 嘿    - 嗨
- Hey! - Hey.
- 喔     - 真高兴见到你
- Whoa!  - Good to see ya.
我来介绍一下
I-I want you to meet somebody.
迈克  这是汉克  汉克  这是迈克
Michael, this is hank. Hank,
太棒了  我们终於见面了  汉克
It's nice to finally meet you, Hank.
哇~你真的很年轻
Wow, you're young.
是啊  我
Yeah, well...
我为这个周末
I got a whole... A whole list of activities
安排了很多活动
That we're going to do this week.
一定会很充实的
Just... just chock full.
很酷啊  对吧
Cool, huh?
对啊  很酷
Yeah. Cool.
在科学中心有一个新的展览
There's this new exhibit at the science centre
我想去看看
That I want to see.
还有孟农加希拉登山车
And the monongahela incline,
坐在上面俯瞰
It's like this, uh, cable car
能饱览整个城市风景
that has these incredible views of the city.
还有我听说有一面新的攀岩墙
Plus there's a rock-climbing wall that I heard about,
我也想去爬爬看
and I want to check that out.
盖斯  来  吸它
Gus, come on. Take it.
看  看
Look, look.
这是你的奶嘴
It's your pacifier.
你得给我吸
You should be sucking it.
终於他妈的来了
It's about fucking time.
我一个小时之前就订餐了
I ordered an hour ago.
盖斯
Gus...
把它想像成  乳头
Think... nipple.
想像成老二
Think cock.
想像成什麽都行  只要能吸
Whatever... whatever gets you there.
来  来
Come on, come on.
来
Come on.
你的老爸也不是这麽逊嘛
Your old man's not so bad at this.
这次他们最好别忘了
They'd better not have forgot the
带芝麻面过来
fucking sesame noodles this time.
都等了好久了  我订了...
It's about time, I ordered...
嘿  宝贝儿子
Hey, sonny-boy.
耶稣
Jesus.
如果真是耶稣来  你也不会那麽惊讶吧
Yeah, well, you couldn't be more surprised if it was.
让我进来吗
You gonna let me in?
当然可以
Uh, s-sure.
不错的地方
Hey. Some place.
跟宫殿一样富丽堂皇
Big as a palace.
虽然从外面看像一个垃圾场
Looks like a dump from the outside.
这小孩是谁
Hey, who's this?
这是盖斯  他是
Uh, this is gus. Uh, he's...
琳赛的小孩  你记得琳赛吧
Lindsay's kid. You remember lindsay?
那个高高的金发女人？
Ah. Tallish, blonde?
你以前和她约会过
You used to take her out.
她是个很漂亮的女孩
She was a pretty girl.
还有一个这麽大的可爱儿子
She's got one helluva cute son.
她把小孩丢给你照顾吗
She leaves him with you?
有时候会
Sometimes.
所以你没事来市区里闲晃吗？
So what're you doing, wandering around town?
想找个红粉知己吗?
A lady friend?
不觉得有点太老了吗？
Aren't you a little bit old for that?
不是这个
That's not it.
需要钱
Need money?
不  我不是来向你要钱
No, I didn't come for your fucking money.
老妈终於离开你了吗
Mom finally leave you?
我得了癌症
I've got cancer.
本来只有在肺部
It started in my lungs,
不过现在已经扩散了
But it's already spread.
我高明的
My brilliant...
医生去年夏天给我做的检查
Doctors discovered it on an x-ray during my...
照X光时发现的
Physical last summer.
现在扩散到全身了
Now, seems it's everywhere.
很抱歉
Sorry.
我本想让那个圣女告诉你的  (瓦尔登湖)
I would rather the Warden do the honours,
但是你妈坚持要我亲自告诉你和你姐
but she insisted I tell you and your sister in person.
所以我亲自过来了
So you're hearing it from me.
谢谢
Thanks.
你好
Hello?
芝麻面  这次没忘
Sesame noodle. Didn't forget this time.
要知道迈克几周前才搬进来
You know, Michael just moved in a few weeks ago.
所以这里有一些好玩的东西
That's why, uh, the funny things that you see around here,
像是星际船长  那是
Like captain Astro, that's, uh...
那是他的东西
That's his.
他一定比我想的还要年轻
Must be even younger than I thought.
思科涨了  太棒了
Cisco's up. Cool!
你在看股票专页吗
You read the stock page?
你不看吗
Don't you?
我喜欢看体育专栏
Uh, I stick to sports.
克劳奇麦片  还是你的最爱吧
Captain Crunch. Still your favourite?
我现在只吃脱脂、无糖的有机麦片
Actually, I eat nonfat, sugar free, organic mueslix.
这样啊
Well...
怪不得你长这麽快
That would explain why you've grown so much.
自从上次见到你到现在
You've probably grown a foot
我估计你已经长高30公分了
since the last time I saw you.
我现在穿六号的鞋
I wear a size six shoe now.
爸爸给我买了这双很炫的爱迪达
Dad bought me these awesome Adidas...
我是说  盖瑞
I mean, Gary.
也许我可以给你买一条很酷的裤子
Maybe I'll buy you an awesome pair of pants
来配这双鞋
To go with those.
早安
'Morning.
你好  汉克  睡得怎麽样
Hi, Hank. How'd you sleep?
还行
Okay.
你呢
How about you?
吃点早餐  我们20分钟後就出发
Get yourself some breakfast.We're leaving in 20 minutes.
- 急什麽                     - 急什麽?
- What's the rush? - What's the rush?
我可不想浪费时间
I don't want to waste any time.
我们有太多的事要做
We got a million things to do.
我去拿钱包  你们穿好衣服
I'll get my wallet, you guys get dressed.
见到你爸爸你一定很开心吧
So you must be happy to see your dad, huh?
他最近一直都在说你要来的事
He's been, uh, talking about your visit non-stop.
-他真的很兴奋              - 听着
- He's really excited... - look,
我不想来这儿  知道吗  一点也不想
I didn't want to come here okay? At all.
是妈逼我来的
My mom made me.
所以回去之前我只能装模作样
So I'll just have to put up with it until I can go home.
大伙儿
Guys!
快点  快动起来
Come on, let's go.
换件衣服  我们有一整天要玩的
Get dressed, we got a big day.
匹兹堡正等着我们呢
Pittsburgh's waiting for us.
你想要什麽口味的松饼阿?
How do you want your waffles?
加桃子和橙酒  还是有樱桃和莱姆?
In peaches and grand marnier, or cherries and rum?
松饼大师  不如别弄松饼了
Better yet, Wolfgang, why don't you skip the waffles?
送上酱汁就好了
And just serve the sauce...
别混在一起
Straight up.
盖斯刚刚吐了
Gus just puked...
全部吐在了我身上
All over me.
婴儿经常会那样的
Babies do that. Mmm.
全吐在了我最喜欢的夹克上
All over my favourite leather jacket.
已经会评论时尚了呢
A fashion critic already.
看谁在这儿啊
Look who's here!
我能抱抱他吗
Oh, can I hold him?
当然  请自便
Yeah, be my guest.
你看你
Oh, look at you.
Huh? Oh, look at you.
你还好吗  帅哥盖斯
How are you, gorgeous gus?
过来
Come here.
他好极了    但我想他大概想妈妈了
He's aces. But I suspect he misses his mother's touch.
我来照顾他
Ah, well I'll take care of that.
-你知道吗         -宝贝
- You know...  - Hi, baby.
如果你想发挥母爱
If you'd be interested in satisfying
发挥你的母性光辉一段时间
your maternal urges for a longer period of time,
比如花一个晚上
Recreating the amber hues of Michael's childhood
重温一下迈克琥珀色的童年
for an entire evening, for instance...
这倒是可以的
That could be arranged.
你想去皮衣舞会  是吧
You want to go to the leather ball, huh?
-什麽都瞒不了你           -当然了
- Hmm, you're good.  -Yeah.
但是你找错保姆了
But you're barking up the wrong babysitter.
因为今晚我要去上夜班  对吧
Cause I've got the graveyard shift at the diner, don't I?
我马上回来
I'll be back.
一定要用瓶装水把它们冲下去
Be sure and wash them down with bottled water,
不要用萨斯奎汉的烂货
not that shit from the Susquehanna.
好的  好的  好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
就知道敷衍我
-是啊      -艾滋病患的生活一定很艰难
-Yeah.   - Must be tough living with that.
布莱恩
Brian?
亲爱的  你不会是...
Honey... you're not...
才不是
Hmm. No.
但我爸  得了癌症
But my dad's... got cancer.
-你爸病了吗             - 他昨天晚上来我家
- Your dad's sick?  - He came over last night...
告诉我这个消息
to tell me that.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他还能活多久？
How long's he got?
顶多几个月吧
Couple months, tops.
那麽
Well, then...
如果你不介意
If you don't mind some free advice
我这个比你更了解你自已的人
From someone who's known you a lot longer
给你个良心的建议
Than you've known yourself,
你应该告诉他
You should tell him.
告诉他什麽
Tell him what?
别装傻  你知道我说什麽
You know damn well, don't play dumb.
他亲自告诉你生病的事
He made a very big gesture
代表他很在乎你
In telling you about himself.
我说你应该礼尚往来
I'm saying you should return the favour.
绝不可能
No fucking way.
29年来他对我的生活一无所知
My father hasn't known anything about my life for 29 years,
也不在乎
Or cared.
我何必现在要说？
Why should I bother now?
因为这对你有好处的
Because it's good for you.
告诉一个垂死的人我是同性恋吗
To tell a dying man I'm queer?
我是指诚实
To be honest.
我一直都很诚实
I'm always honest.
你以为你很诚实
You think you are.
如果父亲连进了坟墓还不知道
How honest is it to let your father go to his grave
自已儿子的本性  这算哪门子诚实
without ever really knowing who his son is,
亲爱的
honey?
听着  我知道你觉得他从没爱过你
Look, I know you think he never loved you.
但这也许是一个让他理解你的方法
But it might be a way to get through to him.
不管怎麽样
For whatever it's worth,
别让一切太晚
before it's too late.
如果我需要一个心里师
If I wanted a therapist,
我会自己到分类广告去找
I'd look in the fucking yellow pages.
对啊  但是我可便宜得多
Yeah, but I'm a hell of a lot cheaper,
而且我不暑休的
And I don't take off August.
我想他饿了
I-I bet he's hungry.
我能喂他吗
Can I feed him?
你今晚准备干什麽
What are you doing tonight?
那水族馆很炫吧
Huh! isn't that aquarium incredible?
我可以一辈子都盯着那些鱼缸
I mean, I could stare at those fish tanks forever.
看起来过了很久
It just seemed that long.
但其实还不到5个小时
Actually, it was just under five hours.
太好了  要知道我喜欢大家一起出来玩儿
This is so great. I mean, I love being together, you know,
彼此分享  就你  我和迈克三个人一起
Sharing this, just you and me and michael.
是啊  太棒了
Yeah. Great. Ah.
我们可以休息一下吃个午餐吗
Can we take a break for lunch soon?
看着那些鱼让我想吃鸡肉了
Um, looking at all those fish made me hungry for chicken.
开玩笑吧  我们还得去博物馆
Are you kidding me? We've got to get to the museum.
那儿有个恐龙展览
There's a dinosaur exhibit.
自从三年级後我就不喜欢恐龙了
Ah, I haven't been into dinosaurs since, like, third grade.
哈  我喜欢恐龙
Ha! I love dinosaurs.
了解一种比我还老的生物  这种感觉很好
It's nice to know there's a creature Actually older than me.
不管怎麽样  看完恐龙後
Anyway, after that,
我们可以去高尔夫球场
We can go to the driving range.
不  不  去棒球场
No, the... no, the batting cage
你妈说你击球很准
'Cause your mother tells me your swing's really coming along.
我们正好可以去试试
And there's this arcade that I want to check out.
我听说那里很不错
I... I hear it's really fantastic.
我想我们可以去看看
I guess we'll... we'll find out.
真不敢相信
I can't believe you actually went out
你居然穿成这样出来见人
in public dressed like that.
我妈常说
My mother used to say,
"尽情挥撒自已的色彩  年轻不要留白"
"Find your best feature and play it for all it's worth."
我就是这样做的
So that's exactly what I did.
再说  这是皮衣舞会
Besides, it's called the leather ball.
你起码要穿得合情合理吧
You could have at least dressed for the occasion.
我有啊  我系了皮带
I did. I wore a leather belt.
你可真够保守
You are such a stick in the mud.
怎麽？  就因为我不想  打扮成...
Why? Because I-I don't want to... look like a... cross
纳粹冲锋队和罗伊·罗杰斯的杂交种吗？  (牛仔歌星)
between a Nazi storm trooper and... Roy Rogers?
闭嘴吧  我听得都勃起了
Mm, stop it, you're giving me a hard-on.
希望他能有点教养
I hope he's housebroken.
说实话  这些人太奇怪了
Honestly, these people a-are too weird.
你好啊  翘臀君
Hello, pig bottom.
想不想舌吻我的皮靴啊
How would you like to polish my boot with your tongue?
我说吧
Like I said.
你怎麽来了  你不是要照顾盖斯吗
What are you doing here? I thought you had Gus.
我找了个保姆
I found a sitter.
你们玩吧
Enjoy, you guys.
你去哪
Where're you going?
回家
Home.
回去睡我的皮沙发
To my leather recliner.
那沙发都跟我一样扭曲了
That's as kinky as I get.
开始吧
Let's go!
天啊  那不是
Oh my God, isn't that...
戴尔·威克斯勒吗
Dale Wexler?
这下你知道他其中一个小秘密了吧
Well, now you know one of his secrets, don't you?
今天过得真愉快
That was quite a day, huh?
扯淡  我在12个小时里
No shit. I saw more of Pittsburgh in 12 hours
看到的匹兹堡风景比我这一生还多
Than I've seen in my entire life.
每次我看到他  他都不一样
You know, every time I see him, he's different.
我得牺牲我们在一起的时间
And I have to spend the couple of days that we have together
在汉克改变之前了解他的变化
trying to get to know the "new Hank" before he's gone again.
-迈克          -嗯？
-Michael? -Huh?
你上床之前不是应该
Aren't you supposed to take off your clothes
脱衣服吗
Before you come to bed?
别抓狂    只是...
Don't flip out, um... but I...
我想今晚回家睡
I think I should go stay at my old place tonight.
你在说什麽  为什麽
What are you talking about, what for?
我觉得我在这住  汉克会不舒服
I think Hank's uncomfortable with me here.
你怎麽会这麽想？  他跟你讲的吗
Where did you get that idea? Did he tell you that?
他没跟我讲
Well, not in so many words.
但是  那些沉默
But, you know, the silences
已经告诉我一切了
Told me everything I needed to know.
好吧
Well...
你应该给他点时间
You got to give him some time, you know,
来了解你
to get to know you.
我觉得他不想了解我
I don't think he wants to get to know me,
你知道  我并不怪他
You know. And I don't blame him.
这种「汉克有两个老爸」的事
This whole "Hank has two daddies" thing
对一个孩子来说  太难接受
Is too much for any kid.
我和马克在一起的时候  他很好啊
He had no problem when I was with Mack.
恕我直言
Well, no offense, but you know,
汉克当时还小
Hank was a lot younger then, you know.
他现在长大了  开始知道性取向是什麽
Now he's older, and he's starting to define his sexuality,
我敢说  看到他爸
I'm sure it's pretty unsettling
和男朋友在一起一定很不舒服
To see his dad and his new male lover.
唯一能让他接受我们的方法
The only way he's going to get used to us
就是让你留在他身边
is by having you around.
我们能不能  让他慢慢地接受我们
Well... can't we... can't we ease him into it? You know,
一开始我先友情客串
start out with a guest appearance
然後再和你联合演出
and then build me up to a co-starring role?
你哪也去不了
You're not going anywhere.
只要几个晚上就成
It'll only be for a couple of nights.
不  一个晚上也不行
No, not even for one night.
汉克会习惯的
Hank's going to be fine.
我们也是
And so are we.
现在
Now...
把这些脱了
Let's get you out of these,
然後上床吧
and into bed.
这个还是留着吧
I thought those might make an appearance.
泰德
Ted?
-嘿  戴尔         - 我就知道是你
- Hey, Dale!  - I thought that was you.
然後我又对自己说
Then I said to myself,
"等等  不会吧  不会是泰德·施密特吧"
"Wait a minute, it can't be. Not, uh, Ted Schmidt."
真是个惊喜啊
Ahh. Well, this is a surprise.
所以老爹　你是主人还是奴隶呢？
So, you, uh, daddy, a master... slave?
以上皆非
Actually, none of the above.
我只是来观摩
I... I'm here just as an observer.
一开始大家都这麽说
Yeah, that's what they all say.
接着他们自动躺上吊床
Next thing you know, there they are in a sling,
鼻子吸着RUSH
with a bottle of poppers stuck up their nose
被五个大汉轮流拳交
and five guys fisting them.
我保证  我不会那样
I guarantee you, that's not the case with me.
是我朋友硬把我拖来的
A-a friend... dragged me here.
鲍勃牛仔把我套住了
Um, cowboy Bob lassoed me.
他说要把我带到马厩去
He's promised to take me out to the stable,
把我像头哀嚎的猪一样绑起来  烙印我呢
tie me up like a squealing pig, and brand me.
快死过来  你这小杂种狗
You'd better git-along, little doggie!
那位就是...
Uh... that's my friend who...
拖我来的朋友
Who dragged me here.
现在他被拖走了  真好运
Now he's being dragged away. Lucky him.
耶…  听着  我相信还有别的奴隶
Yeah well, uh, look, I-I'm sure y-you must have another slave
等着被你奴役
You've got to... work over,
不管你要做什麽都好
whatever it is you do,
我就不耽误你了
So don't... don't let me keep you.
那还只是预告片呢
That was just a... matinee.
再留一会儿   接下来的节目绝对火辣
Stick around. The next one's going to be really hot.
喔
Oh...yeah.
其实  我打算回家了
I, uh, actually, I was on my way home...
那麽结束之後  要不要
A-afterwards, how about, uh...
去我家喝杯酒呢  老友重逢一下
coming over to my place for a drink? We can catch up.
现在有点太晚了吧
Actually, it's pretty late... you know.
当「观众」就好
Strictly as "an observer".
开演了
Showtime.
嘿  小帅哥
Hey, little boy,
要不要去我家
You wanna come back to my place?
不
No.
-滚蛋　　　　-你会喜欢的
- Fuck you.  - You'd like that, wouldn't you?
我想你要找老爹吧
I can tell you need a daddy.
我说了  「滚蛋」
I said, "fuck you."
你才不是我爹
You're not my daddy.
我他妈的才不要什麽狗屁
I don't need a fucking...
老爹
Daddy.
我连着3年都当选「皮革先生」
I've been "Mr. Leather" for the past three years.
不管是地区的还是和全国的
I've held, uh, both regional and national titles.
真让人印象深刻
I'm, uh... impressed.
也很吓人
And surprised.
有吓到吗
Surprised?
有谁想得到呢
Who would've suspected?
尤其是知道你的「另一面」
Especially considering your "other life".
我西装笔挺  精打细算
The one where I wear a suit, and crunch numbers,
对客户阿谀奉承的那一面吗
And treat the clients with undeserved respect?
那不是真正的我
That's not who I really am.
那这个是吗
And this is?
这样很棒  泰德
It's amazing, Ted...
令我大开眼界
How it's... allowed me to expand my horizons.
其他方面也是  甚至是在生意上
In other areas too, even in business.
所以说
So, uh...
当皮革老爹是你的致胜关键吗
Being a leather daddy is the key to your success?
一旦你得到许可
Oh, you have no idea what can happen
你绝对无法想像会发生什麽事
Once... you give yourself permission.
什麽许可
Permission... uh, w-w-what,
捆绑吗
T-t-to chain people up? Tie people down?
那是最能让你解放的部分
That can be the most liberating part of all.
交出对自己的控制权
Relinquishing control,
让别人带给你
Allowing someone else to give you...
痛苦、欢愉
Pain, pleasure.
不管你害怕或渴望什麽
Whatever you most fear and desire.
介意我上个洗手间吗
Would you--Would you mind if I use your bathroom?
就在楼下
It's right downstairs.
你找到我的娱乐室了
I see you found my playroom.
-对不起  我开错了门　　　　　　　　　　 　-也许没错
- I'm sorry, I just opened the wrong door.    - Or not.
-你觉得怎麽样　　　　　　-我...
- So what do you think?     - Uh, well, I...
看来你的装潢设计师玩很大啊
Guess you gave your decorator full rein.
要我示范给你看看吗
Would you like me to give you a little demonstration?
不用了  其实我只是
Oh, that's Okay, actually, I just, uh...
想去洗洗手
I just, uh, wanted to wash my hands.
我们都会乐在其中的
We'd both enjoy it.
我一直都觉得你很性感
Always thought you were hot.
-真的吗  　　　-乖乖牌其实最狂野
- You did?        - Vanilla boys are always the wildest.
他们的慾望深不可测
All that unfulfilled desire.
我来让你重新认识自己吧
Why don't you allow me to introduce you to yourself?
真正的泰德·施密特
To the real Ted Schmidt.
我保证不会强迫你做任何事
I promise I won't do anything you don't want me to.
你一说「停」
You say "stop",
我就停
and I'll stop.
停
Stop!
抱...  我没想到会这样
I'm sor... I didn't... I didn't come here for this.
我知道
I know.
你只是个观众
You're just an observer.
是的  我想我已经看够了
That's right, and I think I've seen enough.
所以  对不起  失陪了
So... if you'll just excuse me.
知道你哪一点让我印象最深刻吗
You know what I remember about you most?
每天在学校餐厅
Every day in the school cafeteria,
你总是吃一样的午餐
You'd have the same thing for lunch.
始终如一
So reliable.
我之前一直很好奇  你怎麽从不换口味
I used to marvel how the menu never changed.
我想你也没改变吧
I guess neither have you.
谢谢你招待我的
Thank you for the...
酒
Drink.
我不知道
No, I had no idea.
他差一点要喂宝宝烫的牛奶
He was going to give the baby hot milk.
-他没先试温度  　　　　　　　　-我不知道
- He didn't test it on his arm.      - I didn't know.
感谢老天我来了  还试了温度
Thank God I walked in when I did.
不然盖斯肯定被烫到
Gus could've been scalded.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
你他妈的来这干嘛
What the fuck are you doing here?
我提前从迈阿密回来
I came back from Miami early
还收到了琳赛的语音讯息
and there's a message on my voice mail from Lindsay
她说她把盖斯托给你带了
saying that she left Gus here with you.
所以我过来看看他
So I came by to check on him,
看来我还真他妈来对了
and it's a good goddamn thing I did.
把孩子随便扔给别人
Pawning him off on anyone
你就可以去那个皮革派对鬼混了是吧
so you can go to a fucking leather ball?
-贾斯汀可不是随便什麽人　　　　-我爱盖斯
- Hey, Justin's not "anyone".         - I love Gus.
亲爱的  我知道你爱盖斯
Baby, I know you do, honey.
我不是责怪你
This isn't about you.
你来抱
You take him.
我是在说你
This is about you
你这个不负责任的混账
And what an irrespon- sible shit you are.
听着  我只是出去几个小时而已
Listen, I went out for a couple of hours.
你根本就不应该出去
Yeah, well you shouldn't have been out at all.
因为身为家长之後
Because, you see, the thing about parenthood is,
就不能再随便和野男人一天打两炮
You don't get anonymous-sex breaks twice a day.
车钥匙拿来
Now give me your car keys.
-你说什麽  　　　　-车钥匙拿来
- Uh, excuse me?   - I said give me your car keys
我要把安全座椅从你的吉普车搬出来
So I can go get the baby seat out of the back of your jeep.
我要带盖斯回家
I'm taking Gus home.
不行
No, you're not.
这里就是他家
This is his home.
至少这个周末
At least for this weekend.
抱歉  你的权利被取消了
Sorry, your privileges have been revoked.
别他妈告诉我什麽狗屁权利
Don't fucking tell me what my privileges are.
我是他的爸爸
I'm his father.
你又是哪位？
Who are you?
我也许谁都不是
I may be no one,
但我至少够爱他
But at least I love him enough
我会他的需求摆在我之前
to know that his needs come before mine.
这一点  你可永远做不到
which is more than can be said for you.
快来吧
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go!
汉克
Hank!
太棒了
Yes!
爸爸  看我看我
Daddy, look at me. Look at me.
小心  宝贝
Careful, honey.
太棒了
Yes!
汉克在去年的冠军赛上打进了致胜一球
Hank scored the winning goal in the champion- ship last year.
他真厉害
Of course he did.
你怎麽一个人坐在边线上
How come you're sitting on the sidelines?
我说了我不会滑冰
I told you, I can't skate.
我来教你
Well, I'll help you.
如果上帝真要我滑冰
If God wanted me to be on ice
祂应该先给我调杯伏特加马丁尼酒
He'd have made me a vodka martini.
让我现在喝
which I could use right about now.
这算什麽  「同志溜冰」吗
What is this, "fags on ice"?
这是奥运花式溜冰队
That's the Olympic figure-skating team.
好吧
Okay.
我的电话响了
Ah, that's me.
汉克  帮我扶着迈克
Hank, will you help me with Michael, please?
我是卡麦伦医生
Dr. Cameron.
是的
Yes.
开什麽玩笑
Oh, you're kidding!
我半个小时就能到
Yeah, I could be there in about half an hour.
好的
Okay.
一个冰球队员在训练时摔伤後背了
One of the penguins threw his back out during practice.
抱歉  冠军  我要先走
I'm sorry, champ, I've got to go.
不会很久
I won't be very long.
没关系
No biggie.
对我来说大有关系
Well, it's a biggie to me.
你就这麽让我一个人和他一起吗
You're leaving me alone with him?
我不会去很久
Well, I'm not going to be very long.
我们彼此还不大认识
We don't know each other very well.
你现在有机会了
Well, you'll get to.
但是  大卫  你不懂
But...David, you don't understand.
我不懂什麽？   迈克
I don't under- stand what, Michael?
他只想和你在一起
Well, he was looking forward to being with you.
我不会去很久
I'm not going to be gone for very long.
听着
Look.
这个是今天的行程  照着这个走
Here's the itinerary. You stick to that,
你们会玩得很开心
You'll have a great time. Okay?
我们一会儿再见
I'll see you in a little while.
-亲爱的　　　　-黛比
- Hi, honey.        - Hello, Deb.
亲爱的
Hi, baby.
昨晚怎麽样  「孩子他爹」
Hey! How'd it go last night, "Daddy"?
别在我面前提到这个词好吗
Huh. Would you mind not using that word in my presence?
呒…开始抱怨了
Ooh, grouchy, huh?
照顾小孩难免会这样
That's what happens when you tend to a tot, see?
这差事可不轻松
It's not a pretty job.
但我还是以你为荣  布莱恩
But I'm proud of you, Brian.
居然愿意牺牲皮革派对不去
Huh? Sacrificing the leather ball.
那牺牲可够大
Whoo! That's big.
「牺牲」是他的小名
Altruism's his middle name.
原来此「牺」非彼「吸」啊
Oh, is that what the "A" stands for?
我从没想过
I didn't think in a million years
你愿意为了小孩而放弃那个派对
You'd give up an event like that.
所以我准备脱帽
So I tip my hat...
还是说脱下假发
or should I say, my wig?
向尽责带孩子的你
To you, kid. Huh?
表示敬意
For taking care of your kid.
实际上  我才是...
Actually, I'm the one that...
你要是说出来  我就把你的蛋蛋捆起来
Give me up and I'll tie your balls so tight
让他们疼上一个星期
they'll ache for a week.
这算是惩罚吗？
This is punishment?
我帮忙了
I helped.
是吗
Did you, honey?
很好啊  宝贝
Good, baby.
说到宝贝  我就很想要点...
Well, all this talk about babies, Has given me a craving
一份烤小肋排
For the baby- back ribs.
好
Got 'em.
-我要  　　　　　　-面包夹金枪鱼
- I'll have, uh,          - The tuna fish...On white bread.
双份蛋黄酱
Double mayo.
薯片和高丽菜沙拉
Potato chips, and coleslaw.
还有香草布丁
And vanilla pudding.
上帝啊  我就这麽好猜吗
Christ, am I really that predictable?
没有  你只是始终如一
No, honey, just reliable.
谢谢了
Thanks ever so.
你的风格就不是爱变来变去的
I-it's just not your style to be spontaneous,
狂野
Wild...
无所顾忌
Reckless.
不　我的风格是从不冒险
No, it's my style to never take a chance,
从不放松
Never let myself go,
从不躺上吊床
Never put my ass in a sling.
我是说…从不冒险
I mean, on the line.
亲爱的  不过是一顿午饭
Honey, it's only lunch.
这样的话  我要香辣鲶鱼
Yeah, well in that case, I will have the cajun catfish
泰式炒面
with the pad thai noodles and the...
和木瓜芒果莎莎酱
Uh, papaya-mango salsa on the side.
勇於改变不一定要搞到拉肚子
Letting go does not mean getting the runs.
给他平常会点的那些吧
Give him the usual.
不管你吃什麽
It doesn't matter what you eat.
你一直会是老..
You'll always be old...
老实可靠的泰德
Old, reliable Ted.
真是令人惊讶
You know it's... i-it's amazing
你在这里住了一辈子
How you can live in a city your whole life
却不知道原来这里有这麽多观光景点
and not realize how many wonderful sights
和旅游胜地
and attractions there are, you know?
比如说  谁知道呢
For instance, who knew that there was a thing
在卡内基科学中心
Called the "scream machine"?
竟会有个尖叫机
At the Carnegie Science Centre, you know?
体验重力加速度的感受
Experiencing the g-forces was cer-tainly a, uh,
对我来说  就是「恶心想吐　束手无措」
"stomach churning, nail-biting
的科学教育
science edu- cation" for me.
最让人难忘的是
What made it especially memorable
我们刚刚吃的大号义式辣香肠比萨
was the large pepperoni pizza we shared moments before.
我们能回家了吗
Can we go home now?
那我们不去...
What, and miss the, uh...
蒙诺加海拉缆车了吗
Monongahela incline?
听着
Look...
我知道对你来说这不容易
I know this isn't easy for you.
有个这样的爸爸
You know, having a dad who's, well...
和其他人的爸爸不一样
Different from other fathers.
而看着他和我在一起
And I'm sure it doesn't make it any easier
我想你也不好受
seeing him with me.
他是同志  没什麽大不了
So he's gay. Big deal!
我九岁就知道了
I've only known about it like since I was, like, nine.
等一下
Wait.
那你为什麽不愿意来这儿
So why don't you want to be here?
因为我快被他烦死了
'cause he drives me nuts.
每次我一来
Every time I come here,
他就把每分钟都安排好了
He's got to have every single minute planned.
坐缆车  去博物馆  看水族馆
The incline, the museum, the aquarium.
我小时候可能觉得好玩
I mean, that may have been fun when I was a kid,
但是那些鱼要重覆看几遍？
But... how many times can you see fish?
那你怎麽不告诉他呢
So why don't you tell him to back off?
你试过说服他吗？
Have you ever tried telling him to back off?
说得好  但你要知道
Good point. But you know,
他只是想让你在这里玩得开心
He just wants you to have a good time.
我的天啊  快看
Oh, my god. Check it out.
《天蠍人》  第34期
Scorpionhead number 34.
天啊  我找一辈子了
Holy shit! I've been looking for that my entire life.
-你也是吗  　-在拍卖网上都买不到
- You too?   - Y-you can't even find that on e-bay.
天蠍人太酷了
U-uh... scorpionhead is so cool.
酷毙了  他还能
So cool! the way he can...
用鼻子扎人
sting with his nose!
-没错  　　　-你想进去看看吗
- Exactly!      - You want to check it out?
废话  当然了
Fuck yeah!
你妈妈在厨房
Hey. Your mom's in the kitchen.
自己去倒杯咖啡吧
Get yourself a cup of coffee,
顺便给我再倒一杯  好吗
and get me a refill, would you?
其实我不是来看她的
I'm not here to see her, actually.
你不是应该多休息吗
Shouldn't you be taking it easy?
我休息的时间多着呢
I'll have plenty of time to take it easy...
多年来的东西都堆在这里
There's years of stuff out here, I...
我想我得整理一下
I need to... I want to... get every- thing in order.
就等着给你看这个呢  宝贝儿子
Oh, wait till you see this, sonny-boy.
你以前的保龄球队叫什麽来着
What was that team you used to bowl with?
东方国王
Eastway kings.
你以前常跟我一起去  八九岁的时候
You used to come with me when you were, what, eight, nine?
你还记得吗
You remember that?
当然了
Yeah.
我一直希望你能跟着玩呢
I always hoped you'd take it up.
听着  那天晚上
Listen, about the other night.
我知道  我去之前应该先打个电话
I know. I should've called before I dropped in.
就像《瓦尔顿湖》里说的
Like "The Warden" says,
「电话就是这时候用的」
"that's what they make telephones for."
我来吧
I got it.
见鬼
Shit.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
这可是我第一次听你开口说
You know, I think that's the first time
「我们得谈谈」
I ever heard you say that?
是啊  可能以前我不需要开这个口
Yeah. That's probably 'cause that's the first time I ever have.
我想或许我们可以
I just thought that maybe we could, uh...
赶在最後期限之前谈谈
Sneak it under the wire, huh?
这还有几本书
Hey, I got some books here.
我是同志
I'm gay.
你可他妈的真会挑时机
Well, you picked a hell of a fucking time
告诉我你是小屁精
to tell me you're a fairy.
好像我还忍受得还不够多
As if I don't have enough to deal with.
老天啊
Geez.
你才是那个该去死的人   不是我
You're the one that should be dying, instead of me.
可现在要死的人不是我   你他妈的自私老头
But I'm not dying, you selfish old prick.
是你
You are.
-哇  看啊  　　　　　　　-太棒了
- Aw, look at this guy.     - That's great.
-我回来啦  　　-噢天哪
- Hey, guys.      - Oh, my gosh.
让你们久等了
Sorry it took so long.
-我没想到这麽久  　　　　　-爸
- Longer than I expected.   - Dad!
-什麽    　-你一定不相信我们找到什麽
- What?  - You can't believe What Michael and I found.
《天蠍人》  第34期
Scorpionhead No.34!
真是不错  汉克
That's... that's great, Hank.
你欠我一百五十元
You owe me 150 bucks.
我要去告诉亚当
Oh, I'm gonna go page Adam.
-他也迷天蠍人　　　　　　　　　　　-等等  等等
- He's a Scorpionhead head, too.       - Wait, wait, wait.
-等等  告诉我  　　　　　　　　　-待会再说
- Wait a second. Tell me about   - Hold on, hold on. Hold on.
今天玩得怎麽样啊
tell me about your day.
-我俩玩疯了  　　　-太好了
- We had a blast.  - Great.
看来你俩颇有进展嘛
Ah, looks like it went off in here.
你怎麽样
And what about you?
有看见脱光光的冰球队员吗
Did you see any, uh, naked penguins?
就一个
Yeah, just the one.
缆车好玩吗
So tell me about the incline.
呃  其实
Oh, well we, uh...
我们稍稍改变了一下行程
We took a detour from the official itinerary
去了漫画天堂
and we went to Comixland.
那我规划的景点呢
What about all the things I had planned?
你们就呆在这看了一天漫画吗
You sat around here all day and read comics?
汉克喜欢这样啊
It was what Hank wanted.
你别误会
Don't take this the wrong way,
他对你安排的行程不怎麽感兴趣
But, he's not too crazy about the schedule.
他不懂为什麽
He doesn't understand why
你非得整天带着他东跑西跑
You have to drag him around every minute.
这怎麽叫东跑西跑呢
Who's dragging him around?
我只是希望让他开心
I just want him to have a good time.
或许他的开心  和你想的不一样
Well, maybe his idea of a good time is different than yours
而你也没考虑过他的想法
And you didn't bother to find out what it was.
你不用教我怎麽带孩子
Hey, don't tell me how to raise my son.
我没有  我
I'm not! I just...
我只想帮忙
I-I'm trying to help.
你这下倒是变专家了是吗
Yeah, but all of a sudden you're a fucking authority?
他来这里不开心
He's unhappy here.
他想回家
He wants to go home.
我本来以为是因为我
And not because of the reasons that I thought,
但其实  是因为你
But because of... because of you.
问题在你
You're the problem.
这里好玩的很多
There are many pleasures to be found here.
你连想都想不到
Places that you're afraid to even think of going.
我可以带你体验
I can take you there.
但首先  你要服从我
But first you must surrender to me.
百分之百
Completely.
你会服从吗
Do you surrender?
是  我会服从
Yes, I-I surrender.
「长官」
"Sir".
叫我「长官」
You will call me "sir".
是  长官
Sir.
你就是我的「奴隶」
And you are "slave".
这里有点  有点冷
It's... it's kind of cold in here.
我没准你说话
I didn't say you could speak.
-抱歉  　　　　-「长官」
- I'm sorry.        - "Sir".
抱歉  长官
I'm sorry , sir.
真听话
Good slave.
我怎麽说  你就怎麽做
Now you will do exactly as you are told.
等夏天到了
So I thought this summer,
我们可以去泛舟
We could go white water rafting.
我要去棒球营
I'm going to baseball camp this summer.
噢  也好
Oh. Well, th-that's good.
那感恩节去远足怎麽样
Well, Thanksgiving we could go hiking. Hiking...
我们要去外婆家
We're going to Grandma and Grandpa's.
行  那就耶诞了
Okay, that takes us to Christmas.
耶诞节去滑雪吧
Christmas we can go skiing.
你怎麽还不明白呢
You just don't get it, do you?
迈克说  你不怎麽开心
Michael told me you weren't having a very good time.
我之前还不相信
And I didn't want to believe him.
我想尽办法  就想让你
You know, I was just trying really hard to...
没错  爸爸
That's just it, Dad.
你就是想太多了
You just try too hard.
大概是吧
Yeah, I guess I do.
可能是因为我们很少见面
I suppose that's because I don't get to see you very often.
你住那边  而我在这
You live out there, and I'm back here.
每次能和你待个几天
So for those few days that I'm lucky enough to have you,
我就想弄得特别点
I just want it to be something special.
好歹做点什麽
Some... something.
能让你记住我
So you remember me.
让你别忘了我
So you won't forget me.
和你在一起时  是我甩开老妈和盖瑞
When I'm with you, I'm getting away from Mom and Gary
还有学校的那些狗屁压力
And all that bullshit stress happens at school.
我只想放轻松
And, I mean, I just want to hang out.
不用老是想着
Not have to worry about doing something
每分每秒要干什麽
every single minute of my day.
就好比躺着看漫画吗
You mean just like lying around, reading comics?
对啊
Yeah.
当我想的时候
I mean, if I feel like it.
美航飞往波特兰的1815次班机
American Airlines flight 1815 to Portland
现在开始登机
Is now ready for boarding.
美航
American Airlines...
你该走了
That's you.
晚上打给我
Call me tonight.
不管多晚
No matter how late it is.
好的
Okay, I will.
再见  汉克
Bye, Hank.
下一位
Next.
谢谢你送的天蠍人
Thanks for the scorpionhead.
再见
Bye-bye.
下一位请上前来
Next person in line, please.
其实我不介意当後母
You know, I actually don't mind being a stepmother.
你没有爸爸
For someone who had never had a father,
可是爸爸经倒懂得不少
you sure know a lot about being one.
我是假想
Well, I just...
要真有个爸爸  我希望他怎麽做
Imagined what I'd want him to act like, if I did.
那我们又回到二人世界啦
So, we've got the house all to ourself again.
想做什麽
What do you feel like doing?
不知道啊  洗洗衣服  记记帐
I don't know, laundry? Bookkeeping?
接着再猜啊   老兄
Try again, stud.
你都向我保证了
I mean, you gave me your word.
你保证我能放心把他托给你的
You swore I could trust you with him.
你前女友已经痛骂过我了
Look, your ex already reamed me out.
那现在该我了
Well, now it's my turn.
你说会好好当父亲
You said you wanted to be his parent.
那就要好好当
If that's true, then fucking well be one.
别他妈光说不练
But don't tell me you'll be there for him when you're not.
你只爱自己  从没关心过别人
When you've never been there for anyone else other than yourself.
嘿  宝贝儿子
Hey, sunny-boy.
有人吗
Anyone home?
你来干什麽
What are you doing here?
一会就走
I'll only be a minute.
我整里那些箱子的时候  找到了这个
I found something when I was going through those boxes.
你应该会想要
I thought you might want it.
我和你的合照  那时你才四个月大
That's me and you when you were four months old.
你傻笑什麽？
Why are you smiling?
照相嘛  总得笑一下
It's a photograph. Isn't that what you're supposed to do?
我不要
I don't want it.
等我死了  你可别後悔
You might change your mind one day, when I'm gone.
多半不会
I doubt it.
你知道   当一个同志你还满会出拳的
You know, you can really pack a wallop for a fag.
别告诉你妈妈  知道吗
Just don't tell your mother, you understand?
别搞到她照三餐祷告
She'll be at fucking mass three times a day praying...
肯尼先生
Mr. Kinney.
你可能不记得我了  我是琳赛
You probably don't remember me. But... i'm Lindsay.
琳赛·彼得森
Petersen.
我当然记得你
Course I remember you.
这麽多年了
Although it's been a long time.
你还那麽标致啊
You're still a looker.
谢谢  肯尼先生
Thank you, Mr. Kinney.
叫我杰克就好
Jack.
你以为你还是万人迷吗？
What, do you still think you're a ladies' man?
儿子长得真好
You have yourself a beautiful son.
我差不多该走了
Well, I guess I'll be on my way.
还有个人  想让你见见
There's someone else I want you to say hello to.
这是你孙子
Your grandson.
我孙子？
My grandson?
这到底怎麽回事
What the fuck's going on?
你跟我开玩笑吗  宝贝儿子？
Are you screwing with me, sunny-boy?
没开玩笑
No, I'm not screwing with you.
杰克  想抱抱他吗
Jack, would you like to hold him?
噢  我
Oh, I...
我好久没抱过小孩了  不过
It's been a while, you know, since I held a baby, but...
好啊
Yeah.
你好
Hi.
他叫盖斯
His name's Gus.
盖斯
Gus.
485009ae0f8546acb2ea26a1f8f189a7